"Independent Prefectural Committee"
"Regarding female student's suicide, bul--
determined to not have been a factor"
Aiko?
Hey... Who am I?
You're Honoka.
Huh?
The name of the person
who that thing is based on.
Aiko died and her bonds
led Honoka back to you.
I'm sorry.
I cannot save you.
It's been a minute. I guess since the fire...
Where's Koyanagi? I was sure she'd come.
So, she doesn't want to
be involved with us anymore?
She must really not like us.
No, it's not like that.
What did you want to talk to us about, Shuichi?
I'll be frank.
I want you to give me all
the coins you've gathered so far.
You guys can't fight.
Leave the rest of it to us
and return to your normal lives.
Here's hoping you'll all agree to it.
Shuichi. I still think you are a kind person.
Thank you for protecting us in the mountains.
We only become one once,
but I know I will never forget it.
You sure you didn't have anything to say to her?
Like what? Yoshioka and I
live in different worlds now.
And I haven't done
anything that deserves thanks.
His whole attitude seems different, huh?
Yeah. If we leave him be, at this rate...
Yoshioka. You made the right call.
We'll skip school tomorrow
and go into the mountains.
What a weird thing for an honors student to say.
If you've got something to say, say it.
Hmm...
Why don't we rent a movie or something?
We can watch it at your place.
Huh?
Then we can head into
the mountains the next morning.
Umm, but...
No?
Okay then, I'll go home.
It doesn't matter to me.
But that's the end of us.
We only lasted one summer.
We'll forget everything that happened
and go back to how we were before.
Okay. Come over then.
"We two are one," right?
I'll always protect you.
Help me, till the end.
I don't plan on simply being protected by you.
I know. But...
...that's what I want to do.
Shuichi has changed.
And I changed him.
We can't truly become one as we are now.
There's something I need to know first.
Hold on, I just need to clean up really quick.
Weird... What is this?
And what happened recently...
There's something about
Shuichi that's not normal.
Come on in.
Shuichi, this house...
I know, it's cramped but make yourself at home.
There's a couch if you want to sit down.
That's not what I meant.
Oh, don't worry about my parents.
They both work.
I don't get it. Doesn't he see how this room is?
Hey, Shuichi?
What?
So... Your parents come
home late every night, right?
Yeah. I always eat dinner alone
and then head upstairs.
It's been that way
since I was little--I'm used to it.
That's not what I'm talking about!
Think about this hard, Shuichi!
When was the last time you saw your parents?
Huh? The last... time?
There's no doubt. This is Elena's work.
He doesn't remember
being made to drink the medicine.
She can control what is inside someone's head...
No... Not just our parents... Shuichi's too?!
I'm sorry, Shuichi.
It's all because you met us...
Cl... air...?
It's okay. Do whatever you want.
What was that?!
Shuichi...?
Wha--?!
This is Kagaya.
I've released you from the pact.
We no longer have any kind of relationship.
Come to the parking lot at the mall,
tomorrow evening at five.
We'll hand over all the coins we have.
Both of you must come. Good bye.
How was that, Yoshioka?
Good, thank you, Koyanagi.
None of us, or Shuichi,
should continue collecting coins.
We'll give what we have to Elena...
...and she'll put an end
to this game as quickly as possible.
That's for the best.
What time did Elena say?
Tomorrow evening at five,
at the riverbank in town.
Where's Yoshioka?
I haven't seen her. I guess she's absent.
What are they up to...?
Shuichi, are you okay?
You don't have to talk
about it if you don't want to...
...but you've been strange ever since last night.
Ah, yeah. Sorry.
I don't really understand myself.
I'll talk about it once I've sorted things out.
Okay.
Is that what Elena used to look like?
Why was she at my house?
It felt like she was trying to protect me.
I'll keep an eye on him.
It's not your fault.
It was inevitable that
Aiko's classmate would be erased.
But if I had used the process
like I did with Shuichi,
I might have saved their lives, at least.
Did revenge for Aiko keep me from doing that?
No. Each time you use the process,
it reduces your power.
And reduces our chances of defeating
that thing by the same amount.
There is no other reason.
Is everything the same with Shuichi?
Yes. During the fight, he pointed a gun at me.
He shouldn't remember anything about our bond.
Good. If that thing becomes
aware of Shuichi again
and uses that bond to remember everything...
...this world will end.
"Academic Advisor"
That's all. Just be sure to get
the documents in before the deadline.
Okay.
How do you feel about leaving this town?
You still have more than
half a year till graduation, though.
Hmm...
I'm definitely going to miss everyone.
Oh!
I'll try to find Yoshioka by scent.
Mmm-hmm.
I don't like being spied on.
Not waterproof, huh?
Damn, I guess you can't contact Koyanagi, huh?
Psh.
Let me give you a tip.
You always look so detached,
yet you go through all this trouble.
Huh?!
You'd probably have more fun
if you played hard to get.
Fucking slut...
I took care of her.
Where should I meet up with you?
"Read"
No. I'm not giving you the coins.
Isao...
Don't act all friendly with me!
Let it go, Isao. You're not a fighter.
--The riverbank. Yoshioka will be there.
--What?!
Thank you.
I guess we won't see
each other after graduation.
The riverbank?! Damn, I might not make it!
Uh... Hey!
Thanks for waiting.
Um... Here.
How has Shuichi been since the fight?
How has he been...?
If you say... anything...
to him, you're over. Got it?
Elena, I--
You did it to protect me. Didn't you?
Shuichi, what are you...?
Leave. Your errand here is finished.
Did she just give you the coins?
So, you're not going to answer...
Well, I'm not going to run away this time.
Stop. Here is fine.
Thank you. But why did you--
Just go!
I don't know what's going on,
but Shuichi is waiting for you, right?
I've always been... watching him.
It came back to me last night.
It was only a small fragment,
but I remembered something from before all this.
If it's true, then everything
I've known up till now was wrong.
You didn't bring me into this...
Was it I who brought you into it...?
I don't know. You're overthinking things.
I'd like to hear more about it, too.
Clair!
I'm sorry, but I've done some investigating.
Shuichi, there is a connection in
your past that I think you've forgotten.
Do either of you recognize this?
Huh?
"I saw Elena today."
Shuichi, no!
Stop remembering!
No!
I won't let you steal them again.
Take this and get out of here!
Get inside!
I've been protected
by your kindness, bound by it,
kept from the truth all this time...
...but it ends now!
Ever since last night, I keep thinking...
Was that really some way of protecting me, too?
I know what I've done is terrible.
I'm not going to make excuses.
When I did it, I knew what it meant...
I'm sorry, Shuichi.
Forget your powers, and everything else--
Live a normal life.
Naoto and I will take care of it.
It's the same as in my memories.
You have the same sad scent as Clair.
You don't have to cry anymore.
You two can stop trying
to carry everything on your shoulders.
I am an empty monster. But because I am empty...
You could become one with me.
You gave me a place where I belonged.
Entering the emptiness inside of
you filled the emptiness inside of me.
Let's go, Clair!
Okay!
You bitch!
You two...
Hey...
Who am I?
You... are...
Ho... no...
No! It's not her!
That thing is something else entirely!
Hey...
Shuichi!
What are these things?!
Elena!
"I saw Elena today."
A monster? Then there's no point in asking...
I am only interested in
the bonds between people.
As long as they don't come... to the place...
Wait...
I don't care about monsters.
Wait. What is "the place"?
Was... Was that...?
To the place where the spaceship crashed?
You do not need to know that!
I met the alien recently,
and this is what I told him:
I'm going to get the 100 coins
before anyone else.
Clair and I are going
to put an end to this game.
And...
I will bear the weight of
the crimes you had to commit!
That must be why I chose to take this form!
Calm down.
We're going to end this game.
That's right. I could always feel it.
There is an incredible story
being played out in this town.
And I'm not the main character.
Maybe I should step off the stage of this story
and return to a normal life... But...
I haven't seen you two
for a while. You look good.
Well, shall we head off to that crash site?
--Yeah.
--Yes.
I'm not the main character...
But when it comes time for the climax...
...we two might be able to find the answer.
We have to believe.